

# **OSINACHI AGBOEZE**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER AND UI/UX DESIGNER

#### **EDUCATION**

2016-2022

Student at University of Nigeria Nsukka,
Electronic Engineering Bachelor's Degree.
Activities learnt in school: Control
Engineering, MATLAB, Microprocessors and
Microcontroller Systems, Digital Signal
Processing, Advanced Engineering
Mathematics, Circuit Theory.

#### **ABOUT**

I'm a final year student of Electronic Engineering in University of Nigeria Nsukka. I have over 2 years experience in UI/UX Design and 6months experience in Frontend Web Development. My tech tools for UI/UX includes: Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator. My tech tool for Frontend Development include: HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT.

#### **ADDRESS**

Enugu Nigeria

#### CONTACT

#### Phone:

08102806920

#### Email:

osinachi.agboeze.g20@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

Html

CSS

Javascript

### **EXPERIENCE**

JULY 2020-OCT 2020

## Intern UI/UX Designer

I was accepted to be part of the intern at the Learnable'20 program in Genesys Tech Hub in Enugu. It was a 3months program where we where taught and assigned mentors to teach us in the field of Design. Tools we learnt where: Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.

APRIL 2021-NOV 2021

#### Intern at Xend Finance

I was an intern at Xend Finance where I worked

on projects for the company as well as improving my skills as a UI/UX designer. I also worked for their child company Wicrypt limited when they where upgrading the website.

JUNE 2022-JULY 2021

#### Intern at Upskill

I was accepted into upsill to learn frontend web development. The program was organised by GDG and Genesys Tech Hub to train young developers who are passionate in learning about web development. We where able to learn HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT. We where given tasks where we learn by building real life projects.

## **HOBBIES**

Running Watching Movies Games Reading